STEPHEN HARDIMAN.

I am a qualified Aerospace Engineer (Honours) with diverse and well-rounded experience across a variety of disciplines. I have founded the start up X-Aero a company dedicated to advancing the personal aircraft industry, X- Aero has designed, manufactured and tested three VTOL aircraft capable of carrying a 90kg payload/person. The founding of X-aero has taught me how to be a leader of a team as well as being adept into the business side of engineering.

CONTACT

+61(0) 429783830

stephenhardiman96@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - CURRENT Founder Of X-AERO PTY LTD (www.x-aero.com.au)

2019 - Current • Full Scale Aircraft Completed (X-3)

Designed and manufactured a fully composite airframe powered by a novel innovative control system. Capable of carrying a person or 90kg payload

2018 FEB - August Full Scale Prototype Aircraft Developed (X-2)

Successfully designed, manufactured and tested a multi-copter aircraft capable of carrying a 50 kg payload.

2018 AUG - Jan

First Scale Model Developed (X-1)

Lightweight fibreglass duct was manufactured for design of flight control system

2018 FEB - AUG

 X- Aero was founded to be part of the Boeing gofly competition.

2018 - 2019

Nova Systems

Explosive Ordnance Intern

Working in the Explosive Ordnance Team (EO) to develop software which indexes the 18,000 EO documents which the team use to create explosive safety reports

2017 - 2019

RMIT's Unmanned Aircraft Research Team

<u>Team Leader</u>

Lead a team to develop a 36 motor drone to be used for RMIT's marketing team

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019	RMIT University Bachelor In Aerospace Engineering (Honours)
2007	Brighton Grammar School
- 2014	Secondary School

ACHIEVEMENTS

2019 / Obtained a remote pilots license (REPL)

to be capable of piloting a drone up to

25kg.

/ Sponsored by RMIT through the 2019

Jacques Nasser scholarship to travel to Canada and participate in Canada's biggest hackathon Hack The North. There with a team of four we were able to build a security drone which used machine vision and learning to identify

persons of interest.

/Participated and won RMIT's and Leaps 2018

> IOT hackathon. Worked with a fantastic team to develop an Augmented Reality (AR) Principal component analysis (PCA)

solution for Nova Systems.

2018 / Volunteer for Laika Academy where

> we visited communities in rural Vietnam implementing drying solutions for

farmers.

/ Volunteer for the Robert Connor Dawes 2015 - Present

SKILLS

ABAQUS	
CATIA	
SolidWorks	
ANSYS	
MATLAB	
Virtual Reality	
Augmented Reality	
CREO	
Microsoft Office Suite	
AutoCad	
Mission Planner	